=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 19=
= الحلقة 19 =
Look at that.
انظر إلى ذلك.
(Demon's Village) It's so cool.
(قرية الشياطين) إنها رائعة جدًا.
It's my first date with you,
إنه أول موعد لي معك ،
and here we are for the haunted house challenge.
وها نحن من أجل تحدي المنزل المسكون.
Also, why are we dressing like this?
أيضا ، لماذا نرتدي مثل هذا؟
You know nothing.
انت لا تعرف شيئا.
Look at us.
ينظرون إلينا.
Don't we look like a warlord from the Warlord Era
ألا نبدو مثل أمراء الحرب من عصر أمراء الحرب
and his socialite wife from Shanghai?
وزوجته الاجتماعية من شنغهاي؟
As long as you like it.
طالما كنت ترغب في ذلك.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
If you're afraid inside the haunted house,
إذا كنت خائفًا داخل المنزل المسكون ،
I'll protect you.
سأحميك.
All right.
حسنا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
(Demon's Village)
(قرية الشياطين)
(Entrance)
(مدخل)
That was frightening.
كان ذلك مخيفا.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
That was so frightening.
كان ذلك مخيفًا جدًا.
Can we take a photo with you?
هل يمكننا التقاط صورة معك؟
That was scary.
كان ذلك مخيفا.
I was so afraid.
كنت خائفة جدا.
Hurry up, stick it on him.
أسرع ، ألصقه عليه.
Stick on him.
العصا عليه.
You're so handsome.
انت وسيم جدا.
You're so handsome. I like you so much.
انت وسيم جدا.  أحبك جداً جداً.
All right.
حسنا.
It's time for our haunted house's
حان الوقت لمنزلنا المسكون
most favored non-player character award.
جائزة شخصية غير اللاعب الأكثر تفضيلًا.
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي وسادتي،
let's pick
دعنا نختار
your favorite NPC.
الشخصية المفضلة لديك.
Dear Mister Warlord,
عزيزي السيد سيد الحرب ،
congratulations
تهانينا
on winning our haunted house's
على الفوز بمنزلنا المسكون
most favored NPC title.
لقب NPC الأكثر تفضيلاً.
Please throw this silk ball
من فضلك ارمي كرة الحرير هذه
and pick a lady to come up to the stage.
واختيار سيدة للصعود إلى المنصة.
He's indeed dashing.
إنه محطم بالفعل.
Pick me.
خذني معك.
Congratulations, miss.
مبروك يا آنسة.
You may now choose your favorite one
يمكنك الآن اختيار المفضل لديك
from these three costumes,
من هذه الأزياء الثلاثة ،
and our most favored NPC
و NPC المفضل لدينا
will put on the costume.
سوف يرتدون الزي.
I'll go for this.
سأذهب لهذا.
There he is.
ها هو.
He's so handsome.
انه وسيم جدا.
All right, miss.
حسنًا يا آنسة.
Please search for
الرجاء البحث عن
three stickers
ثلاثة ملصقات
from our most favored NPC.
من الشخصيات غير القابلة للعب المفضلة لدينا.
Is that really a good idea?
هل هذا حقا فكرة جيدة؟
All right.
حسنا.
One last sticker left.
غادر ملصق آخر.
Do you know what you've done wrong?
هل تعلم ما الخطأ الذي اقترفته؟
I won't do it again.
لن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
It's okay.
حسنا.
If you like it,
إذا أعجبك ذلك ،
I can cooperate.
يمكنني التعاون.
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
I'm going home.
انا ذاهب للمنزل.
What's on your mind now?
ما الذي يدور في ذهنك الآن؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
That's all for today.
هذا كل شيء لهذا اليوم.
I'm going home.
انا ذاهب للمنزل.
See you tomorrow.
أراك غدا.
There are more glorious days ahead.
هناك المزيد من الأيام المجيدة المقبلة.